(Penny:)Anybody want a drink?
(Howard:)- Sure.
- Okay.
(Bernadette:)So did you spend last night hearing
about this silly parking-space fight too?
(Amy:)For hours. Fortunately,
I couldn't understand most of it...
...because Sheldon was wearing
that stupid robot mask.
(Bernadette:)Howard was so angry, I had
to mash up Benadryl in his ice cream...
(Bernadette:)...to get him to fall asleep.
(Amy:)I guess this is what we get for being
with two testosterone-fueled alpha males.
(Amy:)At some point,
they're bound to lock horns.
(Penny:)I'm assuming these are some kind
of horns they bought at Comic-Con?
(Bernadette:)I'm really sorry
they took Sheldon's spot away.
(Bernadette:)He shouldn't have to suffer
just because Howard's a big deal now.
(Amy:)I know. Sheldon should just let Howard
have his little moment in the sun.
(Bernadette:)What's that supposed to mean?
(Amy:)Well, I mean,
Howard's never gonna go to space again...
(Amy:)...but Sheldon will always be a genius.
(Bernadette:)You're right. And I'm sure Sheldon
will get a fancy parking spot again...
(Bernadette:)...if and when he makes
a worthwhile contribution to science.